Vol.3 Japanese-Style Game Music
Thank you for purchase!

Best Japanese-Style Music Collection 

Powerful and emotional music which are used Japanese traditional instruments, Shakuhachi, Koto, and Shamisen. This perfectly fits for battles, emotional scenes and trailer films. There are many genres of music.

Features:
-Total 21 High-Quality Mastered Music Tracks
-20 Instrumental Music Tracks
-1 Vocal Music Track
-44.1kHz 16bit Stereo WAV Files
-Ogg Vorbis Seamless Loop of Each Track
-MPEG-4 (AAC files) of Each Track
-All Tracks are Royalty-Free



-------Version Released

Oct 9, 2019 First release
Oct 30, 2020 fixed a loop on track 02 


------

Content

01. Kunoichi Ninja Beat
02. Jinrai Houto Rambu
03. Hoshitsubu ga huru yoru
04. WELCOMEB4CK Japanese Edition
05. Breakthrough
06. Suikyo
07. The wind and sea
08. Asian New Paradise
09. Kiyoku Yawaragi
10. Ancient White(feat. Norico)
11. Japanese Hacks
12. Koto An Old City
13. Gentle Breeze
14. Raindrops
15. Away from the moment
16. Cooler Ninjari Ninjarous
17. Kirinoasa
18. Shiokaze
19. Niji no Zanei
20. Lilac
21. Natsu no koi


All music are produced by ISAo
https://airyluvs.com
isao@airyluvs.com

*If you want to order new music or arrangement, please contact to me :)

Thanks.
Oct 30, 2020
